Remember how you can put a funnel together when setting up a destination goal?
还记得在建立终点目标时如何把漏斗放在一起吗？
A funnel specifies different steps a user would
漏斗指定了用户为实现你的目标转化
typically take to get to conversion for one of your goals.
将要执行的不同步骤
Funnels are a very valuable tool when you have
如果你的网站中内置了清晰的转化路径
a clear conversion path built into your site.
则漏斗就是一个非常有价值的工具
For instance, in the case of the application goal for the Udacity [inaudible] program,
例如 就优达学城 [无声]课程的申请目标而言
where the goal is to get a student to fill out the application form.
目标是让学员填写申请表格
Funnels are even more common in e-commerce.
漏斗在电子商务中更为常见
All e-commerce sites have a sales conversion goal.
所有的电子商务网站都有一个销售转化目标
And any sales process online involves a relatively similar checkout process.
而任何在线销售流程都涉及相对类似的结账流程
As an e-commerce site owner,
作为电子商务网站的所有者
you need to make sure that the checkout process works very smoothly.
你需要确保结帐过程非常顺利
Let's take a look at this video from Google.
我们来看一下谷歌的这段视频
Hey. This all thanks.
嗨 就这些 谢谢
Are you sure?
你确定吗？
Yeah.
是的
Username?
用户名？
Nick M?
Nick M？
No.
不是
NM1983?
NM1983？
Zandi pops?
Zandi pops？
Sorry?
对不起 你说什么？
Zandi pops.
Zandi pops
No, okay. Don't worry, I'll help. What's your post code?
不是 好吧 别担心 我会帮你的  你的邮编是什么？
It's a GU749ZT.
是 GU749ZT
Welcome back Nick forever.
欢迎 Nick4ever
Please listen carefully to this spreed licence agreement
在继续购买一个面包之前
before continue with your purchase of a loaf of bread.
请仔细聆听这个词源许可协议
If you do not, blah blah, blah,
如果你不这样做 等等等等
you'll simply not use any bread paste product for
你不可以将任何面包酱产品
the purposes prohibited by an article you know including
用于你知道的规定中禁止的目的
without limitation designed development manufacturer of
包括但不限于
missiles chemical nuclear or biological weapons.
导弹化学核武器或生物武器的设计开发制造商
Tick.
划勾
I'm afraid you've timed out.
恐怕你已经超时了
What? Sorry, hello? Excuse. Oh. Yeah. Hey.
什么？ 对不起 喂喂？ 打扰一下  哦 是啊 嘿
Just one loaf sir?
先生只买一个面包吗？
Yeah.
是的
What's your username?
你的用户名是什么？
It's Nick forever but number four, not the.
是 Nick4ever 是数字4而不是四
Got you. Okay
正确 很好
I'm just going to check that you're a real person.
我只是要检查一下你是不是一个真人
Could you say that for me.
你能说一下这是什么么？
That's not even a word.
这甚至不是一个单词
Hey, how about this one?
嘿 那这个怎么样？
You know what? Forget it.
算了吧
Well, this one?
那这个呢？
Hippopota mice.
Hippopota mice
You're in.
你进来了
Great. I'm in.
太好了 我进来了
8.85 pounds.
8.85 英磅
It's supposed to be 98 pounds.
它应该是 98 英磅
Plus express delivery.
加上快递
What's that?
什么？
Well, express delivery.
嗯 使用快递
It's fast but there's a standard.
这样比较快 但是有一个标准
Standard?
标准？
Standard delivery. That's 4.99 pounds.
对 标准投递 那个是4.99 英镑
Why?
为什么？
Bread insurance. You didn't untick to decline the bread insurance option.
面包保险  你并没有取消面包保险的选项
You know what, I think I'll risk it.
这样 我愿意冒险
It is quite close to the sell by date.
它非常接近销售日期
Don't care.
我不在乎
98 pens it is. If you want to put back in
98便士 如果你想在五个工作日内放回原处
five business days, it will be ready for your collection.
它会为你收藏好
Well, I need it now obviously.
嗯 现在我就需要它
Oh, okay. You want the take home today price?
哦 好的 你想要今天拿回家的价格？
Well, that's about 3.27 pounds.
嗯 那是大约 3.27 英镑
You know what? I'm going to go.
你知道吗？ 我想走了
Come back soon.
欢迎再来
I won't.
我不会的
The goal funnel visualization report
目标漏斗可视化报告
can help you to understand whether there are
可以帮助你了解是否有
parts of your check out funnel that could be improved.
部分结账漏斗可以改进
Remember the funnel we looked at for the Google merchandise store,
还记得我们在 Google 商品商店看到的
associated with the purchase completed goal?
与购买完成目标有关的漏斗吗？
This is how the funnel was set up in the admin section.
这就是如何在管理部分设置漏斗
Now we can go check the conversion data for the steps in the funnel,
现在我们可以在此处的漏斗可视化报告中
in the funnel visualization report here.
查看漏斗中各个步骤的转化数据
This report gives you a visualization to help us understand where users drop out,
这份报告为你提供了一个可视化的图像 可以帮助我们了解用户从哪里退出
and why the road blocks into check out may
以及为什么在结账处出现拥堵的情况可能
not be near as bad as what we saw in the video.
并不像我们在视频中看到的那么糟糕
This report can give you an indication of where there could be opportunity to improve.
这份报告可以告诉你哪里有改进的机会
The funnel that was set up for the check out goal starts at a cart.
为结账目标设置的漏斗从购物车开始
So, the ideaness that we're looking at
因此 我们正在考虑
those users who have something in their shopping cart and we're
那些在购物车中有东西的用户的想法
now evaluating whether they get all the way through the funnel to ultimately checkout.
现在我们正在评估他们是否完全通过漏斗完成最终结帐
You can start reading the report here on the left.
你可以开始阅读左边的报告
This is where users enter the funnel.
这是用户进入漏斗的地方
In this case, there are 21,091 users that enter the funnel.
在这个案例中 有21,091名用户进入了漏斗
These are the users on the shopping cart page.
这些是购物车页面上的用户
We can see where these users come from,
我们可以看到这些用户来自哪里
or which page they were on right before entering the funnel.
或者在进入漏斗之前他们在访问哪个页面
Of the 21,091 users that started the funnel on the shopping cart page, 14,067 left.
在购物车页面上启动漏斗的21,091名用户中 剩下14,067名用户
These people dropped out of the funnel.
这些人退出了漏斗
That means they did not take the next step in the funnel as we defined it.
这意味着他们没有像我们所定义的那样在漏斗中进行下一步
They're represented here in red.
他们在这里用红色表示
You can see where these people go next.
你可以看到这些人下一步去哪里
A fair amount of them exit but not all of them do.
他们中有相当数量的人退出了 但并不是所有的人都这样做
Some people go onto the sign in page,
有些人进入了登录页面
some go back to their baskets etc.
有些人返回到购物筐等等
So, it's possible that some of them will still come back and go through
所以 他们中的一些人可能还会回来通过漏斗
the funnel but they're not doing it in a straight line that we had in mind.
但是他们并没有按照我们想到的那条直线行事
The customer journey is not linear,
客户的行程不是线性的
it's quite a windy road sometimes.
有时是非常曲折的路线
7,024 people continue on to the billing and shipping page.
有7,024人继续进行到结算和发货页面
That's 33.3 percent of the people that entered the funnel.
这是进入漏斗的人的 33.3％
Again, of the people that land on this page,
同样 在这个页面登陆的人中
some people leave the funnel as represented again by that red line.
有一些人离开了漏斗 我们再次用这条红线表示
Now, all the other steps are similar and at the end you can see that there's
现在 所有其他的步骤都是相似的
3,806 people that made it and they completed the purchase.
最后你可以看到有3,806人完成了购买任务
That is about 18.05 percent funnel conversion rate, which means that,
这就是 18.05％ 的漏斗转化率 也就是说
of the users that entered the funnel,
在进入漏斗的用户中
18.05 percent made it all the way to my goal,
有 18.05％ 达到了我的目标
in this case, a completed purchase.
在这个案例中 就是完成了购买
Well, you may wonder now what this really means.
那么 你现在可能想知道这究竟是什么意思
How good or bad is this conversion rate?
这个转化率有多好或多不好？
Well, unfortunately, having more than 80 percent of the users abandon
那么不幸的是 超过 80% 的用户放弃了购物车 没有进行购买
their shopping cart without purchasing is above the average abandonment rate,
这个数字高于平均放弃率
which is around 69 percent according to research from Baymard Institute.
根据 Baymard Institute 的研究 这个平均数字大约是 69%
Yes, it is common for people to leave
是的 人们离开购物车是很平常的事情
their shopping cart and they state all kinds of reasons for that.
他们会说出各种各样的原因
Things like, I was just browsing or window shopping,
比如说 我只是浏览或随便逛逛
but I did not plan on buying,
我并没有打算购买
or the shipping costs were too high etc.
或者运费太高等等
If you're interested, you can find the most common reasons in
如果你有兴趣 可以在笔记中引用的 Statista 报告中
a report from Statista referenced in the notes.
找到最常见的原因
Even though people abandon for different reasons and even though some of that is normal,
即使人们因为不同的原因而放弃 即使有些理由是正常的
it's always worth it to evaluate the funnel and
评估一下漏斗总是值得的
assess whether there's anything you can do to improve.
并且要评估是否有任何可以改进的地方
The Funnel Visualization report is helpful in
漏斗可视化报告在此过程中很有帮助
that process because it makes it easy to quickly spot where things are going wrong.
因为它可以很容易地快速发现问题所在
In Google Merchandise check out example,
在 Google 商品结帐示例中
it looks like most users were lost after the cart page.
它看起来像大多数用户在购物车页面后丢失了
So here, and we can see where they exit to.
所以在这里 我们可以看到他们退出到哪里
It looks like many of them exit the site altogether.
它看起来好像很多人完全退出了网站
Those could very well be the people that were window shopping.
那些很可能是随便逛逛的人
But next up, we see that people leave for the sign in process.
但接下来 我们看到人们正在前往登录过程
Let's take a look at the checkout process to
让我们来看看结帐过程
figure out why people are leaving to sign in.
找出人们为什么要离开登录的原因
In this example, I'm in the cart page,
在这个例子中 我在购物车页面
and I've put a few products in my cart.
把一些产品放在我的购物车中
I then click on the next step by clicking checkout.
然后 我点击结帐进入下一步
And since I was not signed in,
而且由于我还没有登录
this is the next page I see.
这是我看到的下一个页面
It looks like Google wants me to sign in first.
看起来 Google 希望我先登录
Well, that's confusing.
那么 这就令人困惑了
After I sign in,
我登录之后
I land back in the shopping cart and I can complete my checkout.
回到购物车 我可以完成我的结帐
So, clearly the sign in page was a blocker here.
所以 很显然 页面上的登录标志是这里的绊脚石
It's not clear why I'm asked to sign in
我不清楚为什么要我登录
and it may confuse people in the checkout process.
它可能会让人们在结帐过程中感到困惑
The last thing you want to do is put any kind of
如果你在结账时把任何一个
obstacle in front of people when they're going through a checkout,
障碍物放在人们的面前
as you may lose them altogether and it looks like this is what is happening in this case.
你可能会完全失去他们 现在看起来就是这种情况
It is true that these people may come back to the checkout process after
这些人确实可以在登录后回到结帐过程
signing in but that's pretty unclear.
但这很不确定
The Funnel Visualization helps us to see where the drop offs are happening.
漏斗可视化可帮助我们了解哪里正在发生用户急剧下降的情况
And with a little bit of investigation,
经过一番调查
you may find ways to optimize and make the conversion rates better.
你可能会找到方法来优化并提高转化率